Yeah, I know I haven't seen you guys
since the combine, so getting caught up.
Obviously, we were pretty busy in free
agency.
The emphasis going into free agency was
really about adding some veteran
experienced players and leadership and
kind of retooling the defense and feel
really good about where we came out as a
team and
you know, last week got a chance to get
on the road and get out to some some pro
days and some workouts, which was great.
Now we're here this week and look
forward to get back in Jersey end of the
week and starting the draft process and
building the board and jumping full of
full board into the the draft. So with
that I'll open up to any questions. What
was it important for you to add that
needed veteran leadership to this
>> Yeah, I know going into the off season
and prior to acquiring those veteran
players, we were one of the youngest
teams in the NFL. So, you know, we
talked about that in the off season and
targeted a few guys and were able to
land those guys and feel really good
about the team where we're at now. With
all with all the veteran quarterbacks
available, how did you land on Geno?
Yeah, Geno, we had a lot of good
discussions about Geno. Obviously, you
guys know Geno well too and his
familiarity here in New York, but last
year we evaluated Geno as well and
had good grades on him and had some guys
that were familiar with him and felt he
would be a good fit for what we're doing
moving forward.
I think
we're looking at it. You addressed a lot
of holes in the roster, but one that
might still be there is receiver too.
How do you feel about that position
right now and are you looking draft
there or you still might add a veteran
there? I feel good about the wide
receiver room. Obviously, getting
Garrett back and healthy will be big for
us and you know, seeing AD Mitchell and
Isaiah and
Aaron and having those guys take the
next step and continue to grow. But like
all positions, we'll continue to
evaluate the markets and see you know,
is there an opportunity to add
you know, competition and depth. You've
been
a little active in trades. I know that's
something you've done a little bit of.
Mostly though it's it's been a lot of
the acquiring picks and things of that
nature. Some of that compensation that
you've gotten specifically within the
top 100 picks of this draft, could you
piggybacking off of what Cosell said
regarding receiver, could you foresee
being active in a trade market with one
of those picks still available or proven
legitimate guy on the trade market? I
think everything's always on the table,
you know, and those those are
conversations that are ongoing
throughout the year really. But as we
pivot from this week get back in the
draft meetings, our focus will really be
on the draft and as we get into the
draft building the draft board and
seeing kind of what's there. But I'm
always I'm always going to pick up the
phone. We're always going to have
conversations. So, we'll see. Obviously,
you mentioned Geno, but you also have
Zappe and also Brady Cole too as well.
Just you know, how would you evaluate
just kind of the backup and backup roles
behind Geno and you know, potentially
adding somebody? Yeah, we feel good
about the quarterback room, but could
potentially add another guy to the room
before the draft. We'll see where that
goes, but we'll monitor that quarterback
market and yeah, just see where we are
at.
>> you did some private workouts with some
quarterbacks. I know you've been
bouncing around talking to all these
guys. Like what have you been hoping to
learn about this these rookie guys?
>> Yeah, I know it was great to get out
last week. You know, I think we started
Miami, we're at Notre Dame, we're at
Ohio State, Texas Tech and then finished
in Bama and it it was a great week. One
for me just to get exposure to some of
these players. There's a lot of players
we saw offense, defense, some
quarterbacks and and a chance to get
around the coach, spend the whole spend
the whole week with AG, Frank, Musgrave
went with us. So, you know, an
opportunity for me to get to know them,
have a lot of conversations throughout
the week. So, I thought it was really
productive week and feel really good
about it. What were your impressions of
Ty Simpson in his private workout? It
was good. It was good. It was a good
visit with Ty. Really enjoyed the time
down there. We went to dinner, had a had
a workout in the morning with him. It
was good. How do you evaluate a player
there there and he doesn't have a lot of
games played. So, it's it's the sample
size is pretty small and he's coming
out. So, I mean how much of a of a does
it make him a bigger risk than maybe
some other guys? I mean when does the
risk No, I mean obviously we we want the
biggest sample size we can. It's always
projections with all these draft
players, right? So, the bigger the
sample size it tend you know, naturally
you might feel a little better about it,
but we'll still evaluate and there's a
lot of good things to see in the games
he did play. How much do you factor in
just like a player's environment,
especially you know, with the transfer
portal and stuff like coaching changes,
all that stuff when you're evaluating
these players? Yeah, all of it comes
into the equation, you know, and and
it's a unique landscape we're in now
with just all these players having so
many transfers and different stops and
we'll exhaust all of our our sources at
those different stops to get to know the
players better. How much clarity do you
have now with the number two pick in
terms of all the speculation is it
either Reese or Bailey, Bailey or Reese?
How much clarity do you know now I I
feel good about where we're at in the
process, but there's still a lot of work
to be done. We'll get back to Jersey end
of this week. We'll really fire up our
meetings next week and have a lot of
good discussions over the next few weeks
leading up to the draft. With guys like
that, like how much do you weigh
production versus like what you see on
tape? Like proven production versus you
know, like a like a guy like Reese had
like four sacks or whatever, whereas
Bailey had Of course, obviously like
similar to the question earlier where
you know, the starts, the career
production, all of it goes into the
equation, you know, but we're we're in
the business of projecting these guys
and how they're going to play at the
next level. I'm curious with when you
are building the draft board and you
guys are having these conversations,
do you discuss next year's draft at all
and like at particular do you go
we we think 2027 is going to be great at
long snapper. Yeah, yeah, right, right,
right. We are talking long snappers.
Yeah. We are talking long snappers. We
are talking long snappers. Like is that
real? Like you guys are talking about
long snappers. Like is that real? Like
you guys are talking about long
snappers. Like is that real? Like you
guys are talking about long snappers.
Like is that real? Like you guys are
talking about long snappers. Like is
that real? Like you guys are talking
about long snappers. Like is that real?
Like you guys are talking about long
snappers. Like is that real? Like you
guys are talking about long snappers.
Like is that real? Like you guys are
talking about long snappers. Like is
that real? Like you guys are talking
about long snappers. Like is that real?
Like you guys are talking about long
snappers. Like is that real? Like you
guys are talking about long snappers.
Like is that real? Like you guys are
talking about long snappers. Like is
that real? Like you guys are talking
about long snappers. Like is that real?
Like you guys are talking about
[laughter] long snappers. Like is that
real? Like you guys are talking about
long snappers. Like is that real? Like
you guys are talking about long
snappers. Like is that real? Like you
guys are talking about long snappers.
Like is that real? Like you guys are
talking about long snappers. Like is
that real? Like you guys are talking
about long snappers. Like is that real?
Like you guys are talking about long
snappers. Like is that real? Like you
guys are talking about long snappers.
Like is that real? Like you guys are
talking about long snappers. Like is
that real? Like you guys are talking
about long snappers. Like is that real?
Like you guys are talking about long
snappers. Like is that real? Like you
guys are talking about long snappers.
Like is that real? Like you guys are
talking about long snappers. Like is
that real? Like you guys are talking
about long snappers. Like is that real?
Like you guys are talking about long
snappers. Like is that real? Like you
guys are talking about long snappers.
Like is that real? Like you guys are
talking about long snappers. Like is
that real? Like you guys are talking
about long snappers. Like is that real?
Like you guys are talking about long
snappers. Like is that real? Like you
guys are talking about long snappers.
Like is that real? Like you guys are
talking about long snappers. Like is
that real? Like you guys are talking
about long snappers. Like is that real?
Like you guys are talking about long
snappers. Like is that real? Like you
guys are talking about long snappers.
Like is that real? Like you guys are
talking about long snappers. Like is
that real? Like you guys are talking
about long snappers. Like is that real?
Like you guys are talking about long
snappers. Like is that real? Like you
guys are talking about long snappers.
Like is that real? Like you guys are
talking about long snappers. Like is
that real? Like you guys are talking
about long snappers. Like is that real?
Like you guys are talking about long
snappers. Like is that real? Like you
guys are talking about long snappers.
Like is that real? Like you guys are
talking about long snappers. Like is
that real? Like you guys are talking
about long snappers. Like is that real?
Like you guys are talking about long
snappers. Like is that real? Like you
guys are talking about long snappers.
Like is that real? Like you guys are
talking about long snappers. Like is
that real? Like you guys are talking
about long snappers. Like is that real?
Like you guys are talking about long
snappers. Like is that real? Like you
guys are talking about long snappers.
Like is that real? Like you guys are
talking about long snappers. Like is
that real? Like you guys are talking
about long snappers. Like is that real?
Like you guys are talking about long
snappers. Like is that real? Like you
guys are talking about long snappers.
Like is that real? Like you guys are
talking about long snappers. Like is
that real? Like you guys are talking
about long snappers. Like is that real?
Like you guys are talking about long
snappers. Like is that real? Like you
guys are talking about long snappers.
Like is that real? Like you guys are
talking about long snappers. Like is
that real? Like you guys are talking
about long snappers. Like is that real?
Like you guys are talking about long
snappers. Like is that real? Like you
guys are talking about long snappers.
Like is that real? Like you guys are
talking about long snappers. Like is
that real? Like you guys are talking
about long snappers. Like is that real?
Like you guys are talking about long
snappers. Like is that real? Like you
guys are talking about long snappers.
Like is that real? Like you guys are
talking about long snappers. Like is
that real? Like you guys are talking
about long snappers. Like is that real?
Like you guys are talking about long
snappers. Like is that real? Like you
guys are talking about long snappers.
Like is that real? Like you guys are
talking about long snappers. Like is
that real? Like you guys are talking
about long snappers. Like is that real?
Like you guys are talking about long
snappers. Like is that real? Like you
guys are talking about long snappers.
Like is that real? Like you guys are
talking about long snappers. Like is
that real? Like you guys are talking
about long snappers. Like is that real?
Like you guys are talking about long
snappers. Like is that real? Like you
guys are talking about long snappers.
Like is that real? Like you guys are
talking about long snappers. Like is
that real? Like you guys are talking
about long snappers. Like is that real?
Like you guys are talking about long
snappers. Like is that real? Like you
guys are talking about long snappers.
Like is that real? Like you guys are
talking about long snappers. guys are
talking about long snappers. Like is
that real? Like you guys are talking
about long snappers. Like is that real?
Like you guys are talking about long
snappers. Like is that real? Like you
guys are talking about long snappers.
Like is that real? Like you guys are
talking about long snappers. Like is
that real? Like you guys are talking
about long snappers. Like is that real?
Like you guys are talking about long
snappers. Like is that real? Like you
guys are talking about long snappers.
Like is that real? Like you guys are
talking about long snappers. Like is
that real? Like you guys are talking
about long snappers. Like is that real?
Like you guys are talking about long
snappers. Like is that real? Like you
guys are talking about long snappers.
Like is that real? Like you guys are
talking about long snappers. Like is
that real? Like you guys are talking
about long snappers. Like is that real?
Like you guys are talking about long
snappers. Like is that real? Like you
guys are talking about long